

CONTACTS



TECHNICAL SKILLS

Scala

HTML/CSS/JavaScript

React/React Native

Git/Azure DevOps

C/C++/Python

Typescript/Redux/SQL

LANGUAGES

Finnish

Native

Chinese

Native in speaking

English

Fluent

German

Intermediate

Chinese

Intermediate (written)

Swedish

Basics

OTHER SKILLS

- Scrum
- UI/UX
- Figma
- Teamwork
- Communication
- Problem solving
- Creativity

Ilona Ma

CS Student

Visit my portfolio and LinkedIn

ABOUT ME

Computer science student who loves working with people and is always ready to learn new things. I am particularly interested in software development, machine learning and computer graphics. I have experience from web-development and UI/UX-design through my school and personal projects.

EDUCATION



Bachelor of Science in Technology

Aalto University || Espoo, Finland September 2020 – May 2023 (expected) Major in computer science Minor in quantum technology

High School Diploma

Ressu High School // Helsinki, Finland August 2017 – May 2020

EXPERIENCE

Software Developer || Beamex/Aalto University

Espoo, Finland

November 2022 -

- Part-time, part of Aalto University's <u>Software Project</u> course.
- Developing a software for Android-based AR-glasses as part of a scrum team
- Frontend and UI/UX-design

Teaching Assistant | Aalto University

Espoo, Finland

September 2022 – December 2022

- Part-time job
- Tasks: helping students during weekly exercise sessions and grading programming exercises
- Programming 1 with Scala: <u>CS-A1110</u>

Stable Worker || Leppävaara riding school

Espoo, Finland

September 2018 -March 2022

- Summer job and part-time job
 - Tasks: taking care of the well-being of the horses, cleaning the stable